为了那些太他妈的大忙人
For those of you who
were too fucking busy,
这些就是上集发生的事情
this is what happened
last week on Shameless.
我要将孩子送给别人收养
I'm gonna give the
baby up for adoption.
如果有一个婴儿市场
If there's a market
for babies out there,
我会囤积成一个市场
I'm gonna corner my share.
我也有发言权
I'd kind of like to have a say
关于各这个孩子最后被谁领养了
in where this kid might end up.
-你在做什么 -寄钱
What are you doing?
Sending cash
给我的孩子们
to my sons.
frank不会得到一分钱
Frank gets none.
我倒霉的兄弟
My fucking brothers?!
那个婊子
That bitch!
frank和monica闪亮登场
Presenting Frank and Monica Gallagher!
他妈的
(others whooping, cheering) Holy shit.
Monica要是在家待一段时间她就会和Frank复合
FIONA: Monica comes home long
enough to reunite with Frank,
他俩就又搞在一起 再生个孩子出来最后又分手
gets knocked up with
another kid and then splits.
你看起来好极了 moni -你有重新开始吃药了么
You look good, Moni.
You back on your meds?
我不是神经病
I am not bipolar.
她做的第一件事
FIONA:
First thing she did--
就是责怪我将lip赶出家门
bust my balls for kicking Lip out.
-学校或者走人  -你在做什么
School or leave!
What are you doing?
我不会回学校 所以
I'm not going back to school, so...
这意味着我应该走掉
I guess that means I'm leaving.
你需要待多长时间
How long do you need to stay?
直到我能自力更生为止
Just till I'm back on my feet.
那会让她十分的生气
It'll piss her off so much,
她会马上回到你的家门口
she'll be back at your doorstep
in a heartbeat.
将他扫地出门
Throw him out.
You don't always have
F 你不需要总是为所有人负责
to be responsible for everyone, Fiona.
打扰一下 --monica回来了 好好享受吧
Excuse me?
Monica's back. Enjoy it.
我在这里 你不用承担所有的事
I'm here. Doesn't all
have to fall on you.
我不爱她
I'm not in love with her,
但是我每时每刻都在想 要是我甩了她
but I shit myself
every time I think about
她的老爸会怎么样对我
what her dad would do if dumped her.
她也不爱你
She doesn't love you, either.
她和另一个男人
She's got this other guy--
那个叫marco的人
a Marco somebody.
(yelling)
我把他偷渡到美国来 准备给她个惊喜
I'm importing him to the States;
I'm gonna surprise her.
你就能撇的干净然后重获自由
Leaving you free and clear.
当他上车的时候 --我也是 成交
So when he gets in,
so do I. Deal.
他还在拼尽全力的试图挽回你
Can't say he hasn't been working his
fine ass off trying to win you back.
你在哪里拿到的这些
FRANK: Where the hell
did you get all that?
我找到的
I found it!
squirrel基金在哪里
Where's the Squirrel Fund?
squirrel基金是他妈的什么
What the hell's a Squirrel Fund?
在这个房间里你首先要学会的
The first rule you
learn in this house,
一定要把钱藏好了
you hide the goddamn money!
你答应我
You promised me.
滚下床去
Get out of bed!
滚出去 老妈
Get out of bed, Mom!
【贴吧无耻之徒字幕组】
【翻译】NG 胡小贼 Dream 哎呦 五先生 郭巍
【校对】NG 胡小贼 Dream 五先生 郭巍
【后期】Mark
【贴吧无耻之徒字幕组】
【翻译】NG 胡小贼 Dream 哎呦 五先生 郭巍
【校对】NG 胡小贼 Dream 五先生 郭巍
【后期】Mark
? Think of all the luck you got ?
【贴吧无耻之徒字幕组】
【翻译】NG 胡小贼 Dream 哎呦 五先生 郭巍
【校对】NG 胡小贼 Dream 五先生 郭巍
【后期】Mark
? Know that it's not for naught ?
【贴吧无耻之徒字幕组】
【翻译】NG 胡小贼 Dream 哎呦 五先生 郭巍
【校对】NG 胡小贼 Dream 五先生 郭巍
【后期】Mark
? You were beaming once before ?
? But it's not like that anymore ?
? What is this downside ?
? That you speak of? ?
? What is this feeling ?
? You're so sure of? ?
? ?
? Round up the friends you got ?
? Know that they're not for naught ?
? You were willing once before ?
? But it's not like that anymore ?
? What is this downside ?
? That you speak of? ?
? What is this feeling ?
? You're so... ?
? Sure of? ?
? ?
(gunshots)
打两枪中两个 -hey 该我了
Ha-ha! Two for two.
Hey, give me a turn.
去你的
Screw you.
我想射个鸭子
I want to shoot a duck.
等你有了自己的抢再说吧
Go get your own gun, then.
至少给我一个鸭子
At least give me a duck.
我他妈的射死他们
I fucking shot them.
这是我的泳池
It's my pool.
这是我父亲的步枪 你个混蛋
It's my dad's rifle.
You're an asshole.
感恩节也有鸭子想吃的混蛋
An asshole who's eating duck
for Thanksgiving tomorrow.
(chuckles):
Yum!
晚会儿见
Later.
鸡巴
Dick.
(scoffs)
(knocking)
(door creaks)
Monica?
Mom?
你还好么
You okay?
我很累
I'm tired.
给你做好早餐了
Made you breakfast.
已经好几天了
It's been a few days.
加了花生酱的吐司
It's toast with peanut butter!
从leo的餐厅
Got a few jelly packets
打包了一些果冻回来
from Leo's diner.
我可以给你个
I could get you one.
老妈感觉不是很好
Mommy's not feeling
too good right now.
(sighs)
祖母还给你们买什么了
What else did Grammy buy you guys?
对不起 我必须卖掉所有的东西
Oh, I'm sorry, buddy,
got to sell everything.
她还是不肯出屋
DEBBIE: She still won't
get out of her room.
我知道自己圣诞节要什么
I know what I want for Christmas.
我告诉过你不要上去 让她一个人呆着
I told you not to go up there.
Leave her alone.
好吧 那她吃饭怎么办 -一个AR- 15步枪
Well, how's she gonna eat?
An AR-15 rifle.
当她饿的时候 她会自己搞定
She'll figure it out when
she gets hungry. And no one's
没有人会给你买个步枪 -她有什么问题吗
buying you a rifle.
Is something wrong with her?
她好几天都没有下床了
She hasn't gotten out of bed in days.
只是对她所作的自责
Just what she does.
是什么 -小hank有一把步枪
What is?
Little Hank
小hank是被狼养大的
has a rifle.
Little Hank's being raised by wolves.
母亲有精神病 debs
Mom's bipolar, Debs.
就像是南极和北极一样么（bi polar 也有两极的意思）
Like the North and the South Pole?
差不多--好吧 我们为她做点什么
Sort of.
Well, what can we do to help?
不多 只能等
FIONA:
Not much. Just wait it out.
需要多长时间
For how long?
直到她振作起来
Till she snaps out of it.
她总是这样做
Which she always does.
这需要时间
It just takes time.
我希望lip也在这儿
I wish Lip were here.
你应该打给他
You should call him.
他知道该怎么办 --这里一切安好 deb
He'll know what to do.
There's nothing to do, Debs.
和原本的一样
It is what it is.
好吧
Well...
我去试试看能不能叫她起来
I'll see if I can get her up.
ian 不要
Ian, don't...
Hey, Monica.
我想今晚去那家酒吧
I want to go back to that bar tonight.
你知道 你带我去的那家
You know, the one you took me to?
你会和我一起去么
Will you go with me?
别这样 会很有趣的
Come on, it'll be fun.
你可以穿那件紫色的衬衫
You could wear that purple shirt.
求你了 monica
Come on, Monica.
你想要咖啡么
Here, you want some coffee?
Mmm.
亲爱的 母亲需要休息
Honey, Mom needs to rest.
求你了
Please?
好吧
All right.
(sighs)
抑郁症是会遗传的
DEBBIE:
Depression is hereditary.
妈的
Holy shit!
看一下
Look up the 10/22
鲁格步枪
Ruger target tactical rifle.
滚远点 昨晚你已经用电脑了
Get away from me. You had
your turn all last night.
geraldo 是F --只是想问问你
Geraldo, it's Fiona Gallaher.
Was just wondering if you...
滚远点
Get away from me!
有什么额外可提供的工作么
...have any extra
shifts available?
她起床了么
Did she get up?
等一下 geraldo
FIONA:
Uh, hang on a sec, Geraldo.
我需要你将泳池抽干 有无家可归的人
Hey, I need you to take the pool
down-- there's homeless guy's
在里面洗澡 --我不能 我的去工作
bathing in it again.
I can't. Got to get to work.
妈的 对不起
Shit. Uh, sorry.
任何事儿都可以--打扫 前桌招待
Anything would be great--
cleaning, front desk.
做什么都行
Whatever you got.
我认为我很失望
I think I'm depressed.
我最近感觉很不爽
I've been feeling
kind of funky lately.
这意味着你经期快来了
Means you're gonna
get your period soon.
是么
It does?
你最近都不要穿白色的
Don't wear white for a while.
太难看了 好的 --你会将我的名字保留在名单上么
That sucks. All right, will you
keep my name on the list?
谢谢你 geraldo -你好 亲爱的老爸
Thanks, Geraldo.
Hello, my tribe.
我的经期快要来了
Daddy! I'm gonna get
my period soon.
我现在没有时间关心那个 debs
No time for that now, Debs.
我修好了别克
I fixed the Buick!
就像是新的一样
It's good as new!
你的母亲在楼上么
Is, uh... is
your mother upstairs?
别让她喝醉了 那只会让事情更糟
Don't be getting her drunk  it only
makes things worse. It says depression
人们说沮丧其实是月经的症状
is a symptom of menses.
debs 不要去相信电脑上的鬼话
Debs, wipe the memory on the computer.
拿去到sam先生的当铺当掉吧
Take it down to
Mr. Sam's Pawnshop.
去看看能当多少钱 -什么 不
See how much you can get for it.
What? No.
我的X-box也要么 --所有的一切
My X-box, too?
Everything.
祖母给我们买的这些东西 -好吧 自从monica
Grammy bought us that stuff.
Yeah? Well, we have no money
偷了我们的存款之后 我们就没钱了
since Monica stole the Squirrel Fund,
但是我们需要食物
and we need to eat!
lip明天会回来
Is Lip coming home
过感恩节么
for Thanksgiving tomorrow?
我不知道
I don't know.
现在赶紧去  当你回来的时候
Now, go. And when you get back,
take the pool down
在它结冰之前 将泳池的水抽干 --我不知道怎么弄
before it freezes and cracks.
I don't know how!
你会弄明白的 没那么难
You'll figure it out;
it's not that hard.
Lip?
走吧
Go.
(sighs)
monica 起来
Monica, get up.
我们准备搞一个公路旅游
We're going on a road trip.
不 不 我们准备去看clayton
No. No.
We're gonna go see Clayton.
moni --不
Moni...
No!
从兔子洞里赶紧出来
Back out of the rabbit hole.
别这样
Come on... up!
你自己去吧
(grunts):
Up you go!
我需要你的帮助 记得么
I need your help.
Remember,
我告诉过你在我的母亲死之前 她给把所有钱
I told you my mother mailed all
her money to my brothers
都寄给了我的兄弟  -frank 让我一个人呆着
before she died?
Frank, leave me alone.
好吧 那是我的钱
Well, that's ny money.
我应得的
I deserve it.
当她快死的时候是我陪在她的身边
I was with her on her death bed.
我付了医院的账单
I paid the hospital bills
而且还举行了一个葬礼
and made the funeral arrangements.
(Monica grunts)
(sighs)
真臭
P.U.!
成熟点
A little ripe there.
We better
你最好先洗个澡
get you in the shower.
不用 Frank 别
No, Frank, please...
亲爱的 我需要你在
Honey, I need you to work
Clayton身上施展美女计
your feminine wiles on Clayton.
他一直对你有意思
He's always had a woody for you.
(grunts)
你要对她干嘛？
What are you doing with her?
带她出去
Getting her out of the house.
来点阳光，来点维生素D（阳光照射可产生维生素D）
A little sunshine.
A little vitamin D.
-她需要继续吃她的药
-我才是她老公
She needs to go back on her meds.
I'm her husband.
我知道什么对她最好
I think I know what's best.
好了 你准备好了么
Okay, you ready?
你可不能躺在这
You can't lie down in the shower.
而且
Also, you never use
toilet paper on your dick
你尿完了之后也不需要用纸擦你的鸡巴
after you take a piss.
你抖一抖，甩几滴出来，冲掉就行了
You tap the end, let the
drops fall off, flush.
- 这很像是当爹的话
- 这真的是
- That's very fatherly.
- Is that really? - Yeah.
你想告诉你孩子的话么
What you want to tell your kid?
嗯，如果这能让他
Well, if it'll prevent him from
不被人锁在更衣间里
being heckled in the locker room
当然，一定要告诉他
by other guys, absolutely.
为什么领养家长非要你做这么个
Why'd the parents get you to make this
-傻不拉及的玩意
-额 他们没有
stupid video anyway？
Oh, they didn't.
我自己的主意
I thought of it on my own.
我想给我儿子留几手好让他能活下去
I wanted to give my son
some tools to survive.
我是mandy
Hi. I'm Mandy.
我不是你亲娘
I'm not your real mom.
她不想和你有任何的关系
She didn't want anything
to do with you.
-你凑什么热闹
-我肚子里的孩子还没成型 可能八个细胞那么大吧
Look who's talking. Well, mine was barely a baby.
Like, eight cells or something.
-你干什么
-你看我像在干什么
What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing?
别闹了 我们得录完像
Hey, come on, we need to finish the video.
Wouldn't it be cool if
如果你一边被口交一边和你孩子说话是不是很爽
you're getting a blow job and talking
to your kid at the same time?
额 我觉得等会再录也行
Yeah, I guess we can
finish the video later.
你知道
You know, this will be
这是咱俩第三次上床
the third time we've been together.
Mm-hmm.
通常第三次之后
Usually after the third
time, I either stop
要么拉倒 要么弄清楚我们的关系
or we have to figure it out.
-弄明白
-对
Figure it out?
Yeah.
比如，咱俩算什么
Like, what we're doing and stuff.
额，我觉得咱俩就是炮友
Well, I thought we
were just hanging out.
或许咱俩该结束了
Maybe we should stop.
别，我可不想让你结束
N-No, I don't
want to stop.
那么
(muffled):
So, uh, we're gonna
咱俩现在算什么了么
figure it out and stuff?
当然
Absolutely.
(giggles)
来了
(knocking) Yeah, coming.
看来宾馆服务员越来越漂亮了
Well, room service is getting hotter.
他在么
Is he here?
现在没有
Uh, not at the moment,
但他住在这
but yes.
He's been here
他在这都几个礼拜了 你为什么还没有听我的赶他走
for weeks now; why haven't you
kicked him out like I said?
-因为我不用听你的
-从什么时候开始
Because I don't do everything you tell me to do.
Since when?
你连自己说的话都不算数
How am I supposed to trust you
我怎么相信你
if you don't keep your word?
我从来没说过我会赶他走
I never said I would
kick him out; in fact,
而且我让他住在这也是看了你的面子
I was doing you a favor
by letting him stay here.
真的啊？因为你是这么个正直的好人
Really? Because you're such
an upstanding citizen?
你到底让他帮你干什么 偷车
What do you have him
doing? Stealing cars?
Lip现在很乱，Karen的事让他很纠结
Lip's a mess.
He's upset about Karen.
天天喝的死醉
Drinking like a fish.
他回家就没事了
He'll be fine once he comes home.
你了解青春期的男孩么
Do you know anything
about teenage boys?
你不能逼他们
You can't give them ultimatums.
(screaming)
Marco!
-天啊
-快到了
Oh, my God.
Here soon!
-我们联系上了
We pick up!
Yo, Marco, Marco.
你在？
Uh, you are?
成，我们马上过去
Okay, yeah, we'll be right there.
Just...
(Estefania squeals)
Oh, hola, Fiona.
Yeah.
额，坦白说吧，Fiona
Listen, here's the thing, Fiona.
我想和你在一起，但我不是那堆孩子里的一个
I want to be with you,
but I'm not one of those kids
你不能老是让我干这干那
you can just boss around.
抱歉，但我现在要去
I'm sorry, now I got to go
接我老婆的男朋友
pick up my wife's boyfriend.
你怎么样了 Moni
How you doing there, Moni?
你还能坚持住么
You hanging in?
想想以前吧
Just think,
一会我们就发财了
in a few hours we're gonna be rich.
你说我们能诓他多少钱
How much you think
we can soak him for?
一旦你魅力全开
Once you turn on your charm,
Calyton就予取予求了
we can get whatever
we want from Clayton.
我了解我的Monica
I know my Monica.
什么都能从男人那里弄到
Get anything from a man.
擦
Hell,
连我的心你都能拿到
you took my heart.
从Clayton那整点钱太容易了
Ahmoney from Clayton will be easy.
我做不到 Frank
I can't, Frank.
你一定能
Of course you can.
来点faith吧（faith是毒品）
Have a little faith.
这个世界上没有神的（monica理解成了信仰）
There is no God.
不是 我是说
No, no, no, I'm saying.
来点
Here.
磕点faith（毒品的名字）
Have a little faith.
? Hey, oh ?
? Let's go ?
? Hey, oh, let's go! ?
Sam就是典当行里的奸商
Mr. Sam at the pawn
shop's a douche.
用ipad还换不了个鲁格（手枪名）
Wouldn't trade me an iPad for a Ruger.
没人会给你把枪 Carl
No one's gonna let
you have a gun, Carl.
小Hank就有一把
Little Hank gets to have one.
Because his dad
因为他爹抢了一堆军用物资
hijacked a bunch of military cargo.
我们要收掉泳池了 Conrad
We got to empty the pool out, Conrad.
你们该出来了
You guys got to get out of here.
给，去把管子插到
Here, go screw this end of the hose
Tony家下水道里
into Tony's spigot
我们就能把水抽出来了
so we can siphon the water out.
或者我们可以这么干
Or we could just do it this way.
Carl!
明年夏天我来修
I'll patch it up next summer.
See ya.
(sighs)
抱歉 毁了你的澡盆 Conrad
Sorry we ruined your bathtub, Conrad.
没事的 我可以去
It's okay; I’ll go down
Hyatt那的地基
to the fountain in front of the Hyatt.
还没冻上
Hasn't frozen over yet.
你就不能去那个给穷人的免费门诊去洗澡么
Can't you just shower
at the free clinic?
(sirens wail in distance)
我喜欢泡着
I like baths.
从小就是
A childhood thing.
你怎么了
Why the long face?
我觉得我有忧郁症
I think I have depression.
遗传的
It's hereditary.
我妈就是
My mother has it.
额 过来 坐这
Well, come here, have a seat.
我来告诉你一些关于抑郁症的事情
I can tell you a few
things about depression.
你能先把裤子穿上么
Mind if you put your pants on first?
我们为啥要在这见他
Hey, why are we meeting him here?
因为他怀疑海关一直盯着他
Well, he's paranoid that customs
might've tailed him
只要他从集装箱里出来就会被抓住
once he finally got
out of the shipping container.
是他么
Este 过来
Is that him?
Este, Este, get out here.
Yep, yep,
我觉得是他
(honking) I think this is him.
(squeals)
? Two, three four ?
? Listen, baby ?
? You know it's true ?
? There's another side ?
? It's all for you ?
? Yes, it's true ? My baby!
? All for you ?
你的五千 我的朋友
There's your five grand, my friend.
Oh, baby! (squeals)
? You're the only one for me ?
? Do-do-doo ?
令人感动的重逢
That's quite a homecoming.
真爱
True love.
? The only one for me ?
像疤面煞星里的情节一样
Insert Scarface joke here.
? Do-do-doo ?
嘿，你好
Hey, how are you?
? You're the only one for me ?
Grab that...
准备好了
All right, you ready?
(knocking)
大惊喜
Surprise.
哦，别这样
Aw, come on.
擦 天啊 Frank 你在这干什么呢
Aw, Jesus, Frank, what the
fuc+ are you doing here?
用这种方式来迎接你最爱的老兄
Is that any way to greet
your favorite brother?
不，你不能进来
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
You can't come in.
Frank.
Oh, Clayton.
还像以前那么帅
Handsome as ever.
你为什么
Why didn't you come by
不在母亲快死的时候过来看看
to visit Mommy when she was dying,
-Calyton？
-因为我压根不知道
Clayton?
Because I didn't even know
她死之前就出了监狱
she was out of prison
until after she was dead.
我一个人照顾她的方方面面
I had to take care
of her all by myself.
我有点渴了
I'm a little thirsty;
is the kitchen
厨房在这里么 求你了 monica不要进去
in here?
Please, Monica,
听说她把钱寄给了你，Wyatt
don't...
Heard she sent you, Wyatt
和Jerry
and Jerry her money.
是 一点点钱
A few dollars, yeah.
一分钱也没给我
Didn't leave me anything.
-老婆在么
-没有
Is the wifey here?
No.
上班呢
Work.
(popping)
怎么了 Frank,她在干什么
What was that?
Frank, what is she doing?
在我看来
Seems to me it's only
fair that you and I
咱俩把钱分了就成了
split the money, since I
她死前是我照顾的
looked after Mommy on her death bed.
我一直想试试凯歌香槟
Wow, I've always wanted
to try Veuve Clicquot.
啊，我们为感恩节准备的
Aw, we just bought
that for Thanksgiving!
节日快乐
Oh. Happy Holidays.
真的，你们必须要走了
Okay, really.
You have to go now.
-不给我钱就让我走？
-对不起
Not without my share of the money.
I'm sorry,
Frank，我什么也给不了你
Frank, there's nothing
for me to give you.
钱已经花了
Okay, the money's spent.
我用它还了贷款
I used it to catch up on the mortgage.
好的
Fine, be that way.
既然你不想给我钱
You don't want to give me any money,
那你就一辈子背着良心的债吧
let it rest
on your conscience, Clayton.
现在我去一下厕所
Now, I'm going to go to
the bathroom, and then
然后就永不相见
we will be out of your hair for good.
很久了
Long time, huh?
来
Come here, you.
别这样，Monica
Oh, Monica, don't do this.
哪样？
Do what?
靠我这么近
Get so close to me.
你的意思是就像
You mean like when we did
我们在科米斯基公园磕粉卖体恤的时候么
PCP at Comiskey Park
and sold T-shirts?
你那时可是大众情人
You were quite the ladies' man then.
我一分钱都不会给你
I'm not gonna give you any money.
你也知道 Frank拿不到钱
Well, you know Frank is not gonna
就不会走
leave here without a couple thousands.
-哦，老天
-你最好让你的钱花的更值
Oh, my God.
So, you might as well get your money's worth.
Monica，我不能
Monica, I-I can't.
我以为你抗拒不了我
I thought you couldn't resist me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
莫莫莫 错错错
No, no, no.
No, I can't, I can't.
我已经结婚了
I-I'm married.
我已经有孩子了
I-I have kids.
对不起，你必须走
I'm sorry, you're gonna have to go.
-啊
-怎么了
Yeah?
What?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
亲爱的 你不能躺在这里
Sweetheart, no, you
can't lie down here.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
你在干什么 不 不 不
What-what are you doing?
No, no, no, no.
你得起来 不能躺这
You got to get up;
you can't lie down.
-亲爱的 亲爱的  -你对她做什么了
Honey, honey...
What did you do to her?
什么也没有 我们刚只是在说话
Nothing, we were just talking.
怎么回事
Hey, what's going on? Huh?
他不想要我
He didn't want me.
没事的
That's okay.
我是个又老又丑的巫婆
I'm an ugly old hag.
-不是这样的  -是的
That is not true.
Yeah.
不 你很漂亮
No, you're beautiful.
我操
Fuck.
你很漂亮
You are.
我带你回家
I'm gonna take you home.
好吗 没事的
Okay? It's okay.
我和你的事还没完
I'm not finished with you yet.
Marco 你饿吗
Are you hungry, Marco?
他现在恐怕对吃的
Yeah, I don't think he really gives a shit
一点兴趣也没有
about food right now.
好了
All right.
用力 Marco 用力 用力
我亲爱的小贱人 我想死你了
说的没错
Probably right.
你姐要把我逼疯了
Your sister's driving
me crazy; I don't know
我不知道怎样才能让她信任我
what it's gonna take
for her to trust me.
-重新信任我  -你能怪她吗
Again.
Can you blame her?
你另外有个家庭
You know, you have
a whole other family.
一开始你名字是Steve 然后是Jimmy
First, your name was
Steve, then Jimmy.
跑去巴西 然后消失了
You know, you disappear to Brazil.
回来的时候又已经结婚
Come back married.
你这样 恐怕她很难信任你
You know, it's kind of a
tough way to build up trust.
但我真的值得信任
I really am trustworthy, though.
你得做点什么才能证明自己
Yeah, well, you're gonna have to
do something bold to prove it.
享受我的黑木耳吧
Oh, my pussy for you.
宝贝儿 对 就是那样
Yeah, babe, like that.
好了 兄弟 你得让我从车里出去
All right, dude, you got
to get me out of this car.
我要疯了 靠边停车吧
I'm getting too horned
out; pull over here?
我操
Fuck.
你打算回家了不
You ready to go home yet?
你想甩掉我吗
Are you trying to get rid of me?
只是问一问
Just wondering.
不 我不想住家里了
No, you know what,
I think I'm done living at home.
我想自力更生
I like being on my own.
你所谓的自力更生就是睡在
And by being on your own
you mean sleeping
我豪华客房的沙发上吗
on my couch at the Ritz?
回见
See ya.
-感觉怎样  -好 好
Mm, yeah?
Si, si!
别担心 我不觉得奇怪
Don't worry, this isn't too weird.
? Make her booty bounce,
bounce, b-bounce, bounce ?
? Make her booty bounce... ?
火鸡肚子里填什么料呢
So, what kind of
stuffing should we make?
有酱汁那种
I like the one with sausage in it.
那就吃
Then sausage
有酱汁那种
we shall have.
-因为我爱你哦  -谢谢妈妈
Because I love you.
Thanks, Mom.
我不会做任何事
And I would never do anything
惹你心烦或者伤害你
to upset you or to hurt you.
-嗯  -至少不会故意的
Okay.
At least not on purpose.
我知道
I know.
不是说
That's not to say
一些冲动战胜理智
some urges might overtake me,
让我不经脑子地
and cause me to think unclearly
做一些丢脸的事
and do things that I'm shamefully,
尴尬而羞愧的事
shamefully embarrassed about.
你是说你和Jody睡的事吗
Is this about you sleeping with Jody?
什么
What?
不... 是
No.... Yes.
也许是
Maybe.
-你都知道了  -是的 妈妈
You know about that?
Yeah, Mom.
亲爱的 我真的好抱歉
Honey, I'm so sorry.
我不是故意的
I didn't mean to.
只是个意外
It was an accident.
一个他鸡鸡跑到
An accident where
你阴道里的意外
his penis slipped into your vagina?
我的天啊
Oh, God.
Hey.
发生什么事了
Hey, what's going on?
我妈刚告诉我
My mom was just telling me
她睡了Jody
how she fucked Jody.
Oh.
亲爱的
Sweetheart!
不是那样的
It was not like that.
不错嘛 Sheila
Way to go, Sheila.
Oh!
和你说 妈妈
You know what, Mom?
我不在乎
I don't care.
事实上 我希望你继续搞他
In fact, I want you to screw him more.
一直搞他
Screw him all the time.
他是你的了
Take him, he's yours.
让他离我远点
Get him off my back.
Jody 进来
Jody, get in here!
他要进来了 现在
He's coming in here? Now?
我有话和你说
Hey, I need to talk to you.
怎么 你也上了我妈
Why? You fuck my mom, too?
是啊 报复啊
Yeah, payback's a bitch.
-你要生宝宝了吗  -没有
Are you having the baby?
No.
帮着她填充火鸡
Help her with the stuffing
或者其他什么 你们想做的事
or whatever it is that you guys do together.
好的
Oh, okay.
嗨
Hi.
天啊
Jesus.
你想说什么
So, what do you want?
我在想 你决定
I was wondering if you, uh,
把宝宝送给
decided on a couple
-哪对夫妇了吗  -决定了
to give the baby to yet.
Yup.
Mark和Celeste
Mark and Celeste.
为什么选他们
Why them?
他们给的钱最多 8千刀
They gave me the most cash;
eight grand.
但是我想 Jeff 和Alana好些
Okay, but I was thinking, um,
you know, maybe Jeff and Alana.
他们只给我5千的样子
They only gave me, like, five.
是啊 但是
right, but, uh,
Jeff和Alana
Jeff and Alana
会是对更好的父母
would be better parents.
如果Mark和Celeste钱给的更多
Seems unfair they should get the kid
孩子却给别人 这不公平吧
if Mark and Celeste paid more.
好吧 如果你不高兴的话 把手机给我吧
Fine, if you're gonna pout about
it, just give me your phone.
你现在给他们打电话
You're gonna call 'em now?
早打早安心
Might as well get it over with.
我预约了周五剖腹产
I scheduled a
C-section for Friday.
-什么  -我想把这东西弄出来
What?
I want this thing out of me.
-我等不了两周了  -我靠
I can't wait two weeks.
Holy shit.
周五我就能见这小家伙了
I'm gonna see
the little guy on Friday?
是啊 一瞬间的事
Yep, for, like, a second.
嗨 Celeste 我是Karen Jackson
Hi, Celeste,
it's Karen Jackson.
我打算留下宝宝了
Yeah, I decided to keep the baby.
我舍不得送人 我很抱歉
I can't give it away, I'm so sorry.
谢谢你了
Oh, thank you.
你也是
Yeah, you, too.
拜
Bye.
下一个电话呢
Okay, where's the next number?
嗨 Fiona
Hi, Fiona.
嘿 Debs 你脏兮兮的
Hey, Debs, you're filthy.
-快去洗个澡吧  -Carl
Go take a shower.
Carl,
水池我搞定了一半
I took down half of the pool.
剩下的该你了
You have to do the rest.
我猜明天没的火鸡吃了
Guess we're not having
turkey tomorrow.
太贵了 当东西的钱得用来付账单
Too expensive. Got to use
pawnshop money for the bills.
但这看起来也挺像火鸡的 对不对
But it kind of looks like
a turkey, doesn't it?
挺不错的
Yeah, it's pretty good.
闻起来很香
This smells good.
Hey,
我这个要卖给西边的Campbell太太
I'm selling those to
Mrs. Campbell over on Western.
20刀一个
20 bucks a pop.
我不用再担心我会得抑郁的事了
So I'm not worried
I have depression anymore.
-为什么 怎么回事  -和我朋友Conrad谈过
Why, what happened?
Talked to my friend Conrad.
说是抑郁隔代遗传
Says depression usually
skips a generation.
Conrad?
住在我们水池的流浪汉
The homeless guy in our pool.
好吧
Okay.
就算不是隔代遗传
And even if it doesn't
skip a generation,
也只有20%的遗传几率
it usually only runs
in 20% of the family.
20% 这数字还能接受
One in five--
those are okay odds.
我想 要得也是Lip吧
Way I figure it, it's going to be Lip.
他已经差不多抑郁了
He's halfway there as it is.
也许不应该把他踢出家门
Probably shouldn't have
kicked him out.
我是Lip 别傻了 留言吧
It's Lip. Don't be a douche,
leave a message.
希望你知道 你明天被邀请回来过感恩节
Hope you know you're invited
for Thanksgiving tomorrow.
打电话给我
Call me.
爱你
Love you.
留言已删除
Message deleted.
-希望您在丽嘉酒店过得愉快  -天啊
- We hope you enjoy your stay
with us at the Ritz-Carlton. - Jesus,
你是什么 老头子了吗
what are you, an old man?!
我们向您保证 我们五星级
We're sure that our five-star...
我靠 他们还在干啊
Holy shit...
they're still fucking?
有时候是在打架 还真分辨不出来
Sometimes it's fighting. Can't
really tell the difference.
我们的酒店
Our hotel...
别在里面叫喊了
Don't be rubbing your apple in there.
不能同时听两边
I can't listen to it from both sides.
好了
Okay.
嗨 小家伙
Hey, little guy.
好吧 我就说到这儿吧
Uh, I think I'm going to end this now
因为你周五就要来到这个世界
'cause you're coming
into the world on Friday.
希望在你被送到新爸妈手里前
I hope I get to hang out
with you for a few minutes
能和你待几分钟
before we hand you over
to your new parents.
我想他们能把你照顾得很好
I think they're really going
to take very good care of you.
我希望能养育你
You know, I wish
it could have been us.
但
But, um...
现在我身边一切都
well, things are pretty messed up
乱七八糟 所以
around here, so...
如果你想
Um...
You ever want
和我联系的话 我很高兴
to get in touch with me, though,
that, that would be cool.
就来找这张丑脸
You know, just, uh, just look
for this ugly mug.
我就在这里
You know, I'll be around.
不会去其他地方的
I'm not going anywhere.
好了 没事的 小家伙
All right, take it easy, buddy.
你上了这家伙
他是我老公
我以为再也见不到你了
说英语 Marco 发生什么事了
English.
Marco, what's going on?
我这么辛苦跑来 为的却是个妓女
需要我提醒你 你之前上了我妹妹吗
上她是最接近于上你 所以不能算
等等 你他妈的不痛吗
Wait, doesn't that fucking hurt?
什么
What?
-没什么  -Lip 他们在说什么
Nothing.
Uh, Lip, what are they saying?
我觉得他生气
I think he's probably pissed
是因为你上了Estefania
because you fucked Estefania?
-你也上了Estefania  -不 不 不
You fucked Estefania, too?
No, no, no.
他上了Estefania
He fucked Estefania.
因为我们结婚了
Because we were married!
Estefania 拿我的枪来
Estefania, get my gun.
他刚让她去拿枪了
He just told her to get his gun.
我知道 他说的是英语
I know, he said it in English.
-不 亲爱的 不  -听她的 Marco
No, amor, no.
Listen to her, Marco.
我说了 去拿我的枪
等等 等等 等等
Uh, uh, wait, wait, wait,
w-wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Marco 你是一个通情达理的人
Marco, you look like a reasonable man.
我们能解决
We can work this out.
Como?
怎么做啊 哥们
How, man?
Uh, Lip,
去拿我的包
go to my bag.
Yep, okay.
去把我的身份证拿来
Get my, uh, I.D.
还有护照
and passport.
把他们都给Marco
Give it to Marco.
M， 你现在是我了 拿着我的证件 好吧
Marco, you're me now.
Take my identity, yeah.
这个是你的照片 哥们
It's your fucking picture here, man.
一点点整容
Little plastic surgery,
新发型 你将会光闪耀人的
new haircut, you'll be golden.
确实有点像
Yeah, I definitely see a resemblance.
还有 如果E的爸爸来找你 M
And if Este's dad comes
looking for you, Marco,
她仍然是S的老婆，W 你们俩会安全的
she'll still be married to Steve
Wilton, the two of you will be safe.
这听上去是一个万无一失的计划
That sounds like a foolproof plan.
我们和好了吗
We good?
好了
Yeah.
我以后再也不想看到你了
I never want to see you again.
这不是什么问题
现在就滚吧
Yeah, not a problem.
Now, man.
你丫看什么呢 哥们
The fuck you looking at, man?
滚 出去
好 恩 好的
Out, out!
Sure, yeah, right.
我只是..
I'm-- just got to...
(shouts) Okay.
(giggles)
刚才那他妈是什么
What the hell was that?
你跟我说要做点大胆的事儿
You told me to do something bold.
(siren approaching)
? It's the universal blackness,
au natural ?
? ?
? When I rock, when I rock ?
? When I rock, when I rock,
when I rock, when I rock ?
? It's the universal blackness,
au natural ?
all natural... ?
(mouthing)
? It's the universal blackness,
au natural ?
? It's the universal
blackness... ?
(techno playing)
(indistinct chatter)
hey 帅哥
Hey, hot stuff.
你等什么呢
你想进去吗
What are you waiting for?
You want to go inside?
走
Come on.
Roger,他和我们一起的
Roger, he's with us.
我喜欢我的红男人们
I like my men red.
我得叫你Ginger了 红头发的人们- -
I'm gonna call you Ginger.
(groans)
对不起 Frank
I'm so sorry, Frank.
没事儿 Moni　没关系
It's okay, Moni, it's okay.
你　你真的不用一直道歉
You, you don't have
to keep apologizing.
但是我毁了一切
But I've ruined everything.
没有啊 我们以后再找时间问C拿钱
No, we'll get the money
from Clayton some other time.
(sighing)
这里 就
Here, just...
一切
Everything's...
(sighs)
一起都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be fine.
(sighs)
来点啤酒、
You want a beer?
我不渴
I'm .ot thirsty.
没人因为渴才去喝啤酒的
No one drinks beer
because they're thirsty.
我还有其他两个兄弟 我们可以从他们那弄点钱
I got two more brothers
we can get money from.
Jerry最软弱了
Jerry's weak.
他会很快就会把钱赚回来的
He'll roll over quick.
莫妮卡
Moni?
Monica?
Monica.
你跟楼下干嘛呢
What are you doing under the stairs?
过来，过来 从那里出来
Come on, come on now,
get out from there.
莫妮卡 我们上楼
Monica, let's go upstairs.
我再也不想当我了
I don't want to be me anymore.
(sighs)
? The first time ever ?
? I saw your face ?
? I thought the sun rose ?
? In your eyes ?
? And the moon and stars ?
? Were the gift you gave ?
? To the dark ?
? And the empty skies, my love ?
? And the empty
skies. ?
? ?
Ginger 你快点动动脑子
Hey, Ginger, think fast.
(laughs)
你这地方真好
Sweeplace you got.
是啊 我们公司在全国都有公寓呢
Yeah, we have company condos
all over the country.
恩 你干嘛的
Hmm, what do you do?
做房地产的
Real estate.
在迈阿密住
I live in Miami.
Hmm.
你介意 如果我今天在这里睡吗
You mind if I, uh,
sleep here for the night?
什么，你不想在家干那事儿吗
What, you don't like it at home?
(chuckles)
嘿 没问题啦 这对我来说不是问题
Well, hey, that's
no problem for me, huh?
我们可以再来第三轮
We can go r round three, huh?
来吧
Come on.
知道了
我能挺得住 兄弟
Get it.
I can take you, brother.
(both grunting)
好
All right!
(knocking)
我来了
I'm coming.
谁忘带钥匙了
Who forgot their keys?
我把LIP轰走了
I kicked Lip out.
那他去哪了
我不知道
Where'd he go?
I don't know.
你不知道
你也没叫我去找他
You don't know?
You didn't ask me to find out
去找他在哪
是你叫我把他轰走的
where he was going.
You asked me to kick him out.
你说的对 我很抱歉
You're right, I'm sorry.
(both sigh)
谢谢
不客气
Thank you.
You're welcome.
他怎么样
How'd he take it?
还不错
你想上楼去吗
Seemed fine.
You want to go upstairs?
不用了 给你一个谢谢的Kiss
No, you got a thank-you kiss.
就这样
That's it?
那你期待着什么呢
What were you expecting?
我能在你的沙发上过夜吗
Can I spend the night on your couch?
为什么
这样我明天就可以在这里过感恩节了
Why?
Then I'll be here tomorrow for Thanksgiving.
谁邀请你了
Who said you're invited?
我都把LIP轰走了
I kicked Lip out.
我给你拿个枕头和被子吧
I'll get you a pillow and blanket.
(train rattling)
(sighs)
Hey.
想我了吗
Missed me, huh?
想了 听着
Yeah. Um, hey, look,
我今晚上能在这里睡么
is it... is it all right
if I stay over tonight?
半天不见我就受不了了
Couldn't go 12 hours
without seeing me, could ya?
(laughs)
(sighs)
(grunting softly)
? ?
我打中一只鸭子
I shot a duck!
这里没鸭子
That's no duck.
可能是一只秃鹰
That's a bald eagle.
(pots clattering)
(indistinct chatter and laughter)
(Steve sighs)
感恩节快乐
VERONICA & FIONA:
Happy Thanksgiving.
早上好 S
Morning, Steve.
你知道吗 黛比
我们来正式规定一下
You know what, Debs?
Let's make it official.
不再有Steve了
从现在开始 只有Jimmy
No more Steve.
From now on, it's Jimmy.
好的 真好
Okay. Cool.
真的吗
真的
Really?
Yup.
致Jimmy
To Jimmy!
为了Jimmy
VERONICA: To Jimmy!
Jimmy!
(whooping)
干杯
Cheers.
你知道吗 我打算叫你抱着枕头流口水的吉米
You know, I'm gonna call you
Jimmy pillow drooler.
你丫闭嘴 我没有
Shut the fuck up.
I do not.
不不 我向上帝保证 你就这样
No, I swear to God.
This is you.
一边呻吟一边笑
(groaning) (laughter)
你跟这转什么呢
看起来怎么样
What are you doing over there?
What's it look like?
弄来一只秃鹰
什么？
Plucking a bald eagle.
What?
Carl 在院子里打死的
Carl shot it in the yard.
用什么打
那是违法的
With what?
That's against the law.
我已经给他上了一课了
况且 子弹已经拿出来了
I already gave him a lecture.
And took out the bullets.
这上面说 这是一个放生的项目
DEBBIE: It says there was
a re-release program
在密歇根州的半岛
in the Michigan peninsula.
动物园有十只秃鹰
Let out ten bald eagles
被放生到野外了
that had been raised
从动物园到野生
in the Detroit Zoo into the wild.
昨天晚上 我碰到一只
And one of them came to me last night.
他腿上有个什么东西 --是跟踪器
You know, there is something on his leg.
That's a tracking device.
这样的话 他们就可以知道老鹰在哪筑巢
That way, they can
monitor where it nests.
好吧 有人知道老鹰在我们这吗  可能
So, somebody knows that we have it?
Probably.
恩 一定挺疼的吧 老鹰
Uh, it must have hurt, huh, buddy?
我第一枪就打中它了
Got him on my first shot.
据说
Says tampering with a bald eagle
抓住老鹰的人
tracker is
会被依法制裁的
punishable by law.
问题解决了
Problem solved.
Carl 这个给你  把这些证据处理掉
Here, Carl, get rid of the evidence.
(hissing) Eww!
这个我们可以留到周末吃
Guess we can save this
for the weekend.
为什么啊  我们感恩节要吃什么啊
Why? What are we having
for Thanksgiving?
不是吧 不是吧
No, no, no, no, no. No.
这么看 它真挺像教堂里面的摆设一样
It's just like the pilgrims intended.
(distant laughter, Monica sighs)
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
Hmm.
Oh.
别这样
Stop it.
(Frank sighs)
我没那个心情
I'm not in the mood.
你一直都爱干这事的啊
You're always in the mood.
用手怎么样
How about a little handy J?
你什么也不用干
You don't have to do anything.
我自己来
I'll do all the work.
我的小宝贝啊
That's a girl.
(Frank moaning)
Moni 你手得握得紧一点
Moni, you got to squeeze a little.
Mm.
你是该吃药了 是不
Time for you to go back
on your meds, huh?
(sighs)
是的
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
我去给你整点药
I'll get you some.
(sighs)
(train rattling)
我们应该什么时候告诉Ian
When should we tell Ian?
告诉他什么
Tell him what?
我们俩的事啊
About us?
(door opening)
滚出去
Yo.
Get the hell out!
哇塞 Mandy 你还在和gallagher家的人搞在一起
What, are you
Gallagher hopping, Mandy?
你们爸妈没告诉过你们
Dad said you had to knock
进门以前 得先敲门吗
before you came in.
我们俩是要来找个人帮我们开车的
Need someone to do a beer run.
就因为你们俩个垃圾喝酒了
Yeah, just 'cause you two retards
不代表着
have DUIs don't make me
我就得帮你们俩开车
your personal chauffeur.
没事 我来开车 好啊
No, I'll do it.
Yeah, cool.
谢了
Yeah.
Thanks.
一会我们可以去Juan家的杂货店
弄点玉米饼当早餐吃
We can go get breakfast
burritos at Juan's truck after.
(laughter)
- 我还不知道你会弄火鸡肉呢
- 哦 亲爱的
- I didn't know you could do that with
a turkey baster. - Oh, honey... (gasps)
Frank.
你来这干什么
Sheila.
What are you doing here?
我是专程来祝你
感恩节快乐的
I came by to wish you...
happy Thanksgiving!
Frank 感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving, Frank.
他他妈的在这干什么?
What the hell is he doing here?
你去哪了啊?
Where have you been?
FRANK:
Oh, Sheils.
我真的不想告诉你这个
I... I really didn't want
to have to tell you this.
你要告诉我什么
告诉我Monica回来了
What? That
Monica's back?
你已经知道了
You heard about that?
是的
Yes.
Oh.
你生气了吗?
Are you... are you mad?
我不生气 真的
I'm not, actually.
KAREN: Yeah.
我妈和我前任的男朋友搞在一起了
Mom fucked my ex.
你和Lip
You slept with Lip?
哦 天啊 当然不是了
是我
Oh, God, no.
It was me.
- 你和他在一起了
- 是的
You slept with him?
Yes.
没错 我和他在一起了
Yes, I did.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God!
Sheila!
你怎么能这么对我呢
How could you do this to me?
我的心 都碎了
My heart-- it's broken.
你这对我打击太大了
我不知道我该怎么办了
I'm probably gonna go through
a lot of depression over this.
哦 天啊  你有抗抑郁的药什么的吗
Oh, God. Could use
some antidepressants.
你有吗
Lithium... if you've got it?
好吧 Frank 天啊
All right, okay, Frank.
God!
Frank 你别挂Shelia
Frank, please don't be
upset with Sheila.
这全是我的错
(Frank groans) It's my fault.
妈的 去他妈的
Shit! Fuck! Cock!
我这是尿裤子了吗
Did I just piss myself?
你要生了
(gasps) It's the baby.
哦 亲爱的 你要生孩子了
FRANK: Oh!
Honey, you're gonna have the baby!
我去把你要生孩子的东西拿来
哦 我的天啊
I'll go get your suitcase.
Oh, my God!
我要当姥姥了
I'm gonna be a grandma.
是啊 我太高兴了
Yeah, I know.
This is exciting!
Hey.
我找到了 我找到你去医院的东西了
I got your suitcase!
好的  亲爱的
SHEILA: Okay, okay.
Sweetie...
(Jody shouts, indistinct chatter)
还得拿点毛巾什么的
Somebody get some towels or something.
我们马上就回来
COLIN:
We'll be right back.
你想吃什么吗
不用了
Want anything?
Uh...Too bad.
这周末咱俩去哪玩
What should we do this weekend?
明天就是Karen的预产期了
LIP: Karen's actually
having the baby tomorrow.
所以
几点
So...
Whatime?
你完事想去看场电影吗
Want to see a movie after?
好吧
I-I guess?
太好了 Mandy 别这样
Okay, cool.
Whoa. Mandy, come on.
你哥哥就在那边呢
我就玩一会
Your brothers are right there.
I'll be fast.
别闹了  他们离咱俩就20英尺远
Seriously. They're, like,
20 feet away. Come on.
这他妈的是怎么了?
What the fuck?!
把收银机打开! 快点 快点
Open the fucking register!
Let's go! Let's go!
Mandy 你不是说他们俩要买啤酒吗
Mandy, I thought you said
they were getting beer.
这就是一婉转的说法
A euphemism.
快点 老头 快点 全拿出来
Come on, old man!
Let's go! Pick it all up!
(shouting)
天啊
Jesus!
(woman shouting)
妈的
Shit!
(alarm blaring)
你他妈的要去哪?
Where the hell are you going?!
我们得赶紧走
We got to get out of here!
(gunshot)
你上车
Get back in the car!
我他妈的才不上车呢  没门
Got to get out.
No fucking way!
你就他妈的上了我 就要跑
You're gonna fuck me and walk away?
去你妈的
Fuck you!
(muffled shouting)
垃圾 Lip 你吃屎去吧
MANDY:
Asshole, Lip! Eat shit.
BOTH:
Mandy!
(gunshot)
(tires squealing, gun chamber cocking)
(phone ringing)
喂
Hello?
等一下 你说谁
Wait. She is?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
好吧  她要生了
All right, the baby, yeah.
Um...
(siren blaring)
好 好 我马上就到
All right, all right,
I'll be right there.
(siren blaring)
别在里面装太多的吃的
Didn't take much stuffing.
我们应该烤多长时间呢
How long we supposed to cook it for?
火鸡是 一磅得烤20分钟
20 minut a pound for turkey.
我们感恩节不用吃秃鹰了
We are not having bald
eagle for Thanksgiving. Here.
这个这么大啊
不用谢了 小可爱
Whoa, this thing's huge.
You're welcome, Tiny Tim.
这个秃鹰我们怎么处理啊
把它扔了
What are we supposed to do with this?
Toss it?
当然不了 打到 杀掉 吃掉 这就是猎人的原则
Hell, no. Hunt it, kill it,
eat it. The hunter's code.
我们不可能白白浪费
There's no way we're gonna
let the most sacred symbol of
美国自由民主解放的标志啊
( 秃鹰是美国的标志 )
American freedom and individual
liberty go to waste.
我们把它放在冰箱上冻起来
I'll put it in the freezer.
我们要过感恩节了
We got Thanksgiving!
额的神啊 这他妈的要疼死我了
Christ Almighty,
this cock sucker's killing me.
哦 我的天啊 我这太激动了
我都不知道要怎么办好了
Oh, my gosh, it's so exciting.
I can hardly contain myself.
(Sheila inhales and exhales loudly)
妈妈 我才是那个该深呼吸的人
Mom, I'm supposed
to be the one breathing.
宝贝 对不起 我就是有点太激动太紧张了
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I'm just so excited and nervous.
我竟然还出家门了
(groaning) And out of the house.
(groaning)
天啊 那玩意竟然打开了
Damn, that thing really opens up.
你他妈的离我远一点
Get the hell away from me.
对不起
Sorry.
去他妈的
Mother fucking piece of shit!
(groaning)
我们要吃火鸡了
We got a big turkey.
你昨天去哪了
Where have you been?
出去了
你昨天晚上回来了吗
Out.
Did you come home last night?
没有
你怎么都没打个电话呢
No.
You even think to call?
我这不是回来了吗
I'm here now.
我想和大家一起过感恩节
Wasn't gonna miss a family holiday.
过来
Come here.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
你这脖子上有个唇印  去洗洗吧
It's a ne
hickey. Go wash up.
我应该给Lip留个位置吗
当然要了 亲爱的
Should I set a place for Lip?
Sure, sweetie.
我不在的时候 你们最好还没开吃
You better not have started without me.
Frank?
嘿 爸爸
Hey!
Daddy!
你要来这吃晚饭吗
You're gonna come to dinner?
当然了要了  亲爱的
Of course I am, son.
你妈妈也来这吃
And so's your mother.
Lithium?
Moni,
我给你拿药了
I got your medications.
妈妈在楼梯下面
Mom's under the stairs?
她在那待多长时间了
How long has she been under there?
给你 亲爱的 你要吃的
Here you go, sweetheart.
Here's your candy.
挺长时间了
That should do it.
你出来
Get out of there.
你出来  不 Fiona
No, Fiona.
我不出来 Fiona 我不
(crying):
No, Fiona! No!
你赶紧出来 快点
Come on out. Come on.
我不出来
你赶紧出来
No!
Get out of there.
快点
我不要
Come on.
No!
快点
FIONA: Come on.
Fiona.
你上楼去 上楼  快点
Up you go.
Up you go. Come on.
我得脏死了 不 你一点也不脏
I look a mess.
No, you do not.
你还是那么漂亮
她是不是还是那么漂亮 宝贝们
You look beautiful. Doesn't
she look beautiful, kids?
你看起来好极了
You look great.
没错 没错 嗨 妈妈
FRANK: Yeah.
Yeah. Hi, Mom.
你不应该在楼梯下面过感恩节
You're not spending Thanksgiving
under the stairs, okay?
Debs 给妈妈弄个位子
Debs, set a place for Monica.
我们要一起吃晚餐
We're all having dinner together.
和孩子们一起 在桌边吃晚餐
With the kids at the table.
好吧
That's right.
你就坐这
You're gonna sit right here.
好吧  感恩节快乐
Well, then, happy Thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving!
(cheering and chatter)
谁饿了吗
Who's hungry? I...
Yeah.
对不起
Sorry. Hi, Jeff. Alana.
是Shelia给我们打的电话
Hey.
Sheila called us.
我门不敢相信 她这么快就要生了
Can't believe it's happening so fast.
我也是 你们想进去吗
I don't, either.
You guys coming in?
Karen不想让我们进去
Karen didn't want us in there.
他们让我们在外面等着
They told us to wait out here.
好吧
Okay.
她在803呢
She's in room 803.
好吧
Right. Oh, hey, um,
我想给你们个东西
I wanted to give you guys something.
这个是给这个孩子的
Uh, made this for the baby.
你们要是想给他的话
Um, if you guys could give it
to him at some point,
我的意思是 如果你觉得可以
you know, if you feel like it.
恩 谢了 LIP
Yeah. Thank you, Lip.
是的 我们会的
Yeah, we will.
好的 我该进去了
Cool. Um, I should go in.
走
Go!
来了
Here we go!
(cheering)
好样的 宝贝
Good job, baby.
我等不及吃火鸡了
Can't wait to get that turkey in me.
你还好吧
You okay?
-啊
-我们还没祈祷呢
Ah! We haven't said grace yet.
我来说 我来说祈祷词
I'll say it.
I'll say the grace.
牵起手
FRANK:
Hold hands.
仁慈的主
Dear Lord,
感谢你赐予我们食物
Thank you for this food
that we're about to eat.
感谢你把MONICA
Thank you for bringing my Monica
带还给我
back to me.
还有请让我的弟弟Clayton在
And please make my brother
Clayton burn in hell
无尽的地狱轮回中经烈火的燃烧
for all eternity when the time comes.
阿门
Amen.
EVERYONE:
你要切火鸡吗
我都饿死了
Are you gonna carve the turkey?
I'm starving.
我来切
我是一家之主
I'm carving.
I am the man of the house.
我先去洗洗手
(whispers) I'm gonna go wash my hands.
Fiona Lip来吗
Fiona, is Lip coming?
要叫他来吗
JIMMY:
Want me to call him?
是的
Yeah.
Uh,
他知道我们什么时候开饭
he knows what time we're eating.
土豆泥 谢谢
Mashed potatoes, please.
谁要火鸡腿
我
Who likes dark meat?
Me!
哦 我也要  我的火鸡肉也要土豆泥
Ooh, me, too.
And on my turkey, also.
我请了Conrad
可以吗
(knocking)
I invited Conrad. Is that okay?
Conrad
Conrad?
我从游泳池那找到的无家可归的人
My homeless guy from the pool.
来了
当然可以 Debs
Coming...
Sure, Debs.
Conrad 你好吗
DEBBIE:
Conrad, how are you?
Hi, Deb.
Hi.
大家 这是Conrad
Everyone, this is Conrad.
EVERYONE:
Hi, Conrad.
比秃头雕好多了
Much better than bald eagle.
嘿 我们还在吃呢
(laughs)
Hey, we're still eating that.
我们打算煎了它 烤了它 炸了它
We're gonna roast it, bake it, fry it.
随便 反正我们也是要吃的
I don't care,
but we're really gonna eat it.
我打赌它的味道像鸡肉
Bet it tastes like chicken.
好吧 反正我们圣诞节也会吃到的
Well, we could always
have it for Christmas.
(overlapping chatter, loud thud)
那是什么
What was that?
我准备把这些放在
I'm just gonna put all of this
一个盘子里面
然后大家就可以
on this one plate,
and then everybody could...
我了个去
Holy fuck!
(gasping)
什么
STEVE:
What?
(gasping)
给我电话
Give me a phone.
把电话给我
(Monica panting)
快 大家 上楼
上楼
Come on, guys, upstairs.
Upstairs, kids.
好的 我操
STEVE:
Okay, uh, fuck!
没事的 没事的
没事的 别担心
We're good. We're good.
We're good. Don't worry.
再给我点毛巾
More towels.
操 这出事了
Shit!
FIONA: There's been an accident.
好的
All right.
北华勒斯2119号
2119 North Wallace.
她在大出血
She's bleeding badly.
是的 她还清醒着
Yeah, she's awake.
Uh...
Frank 多拿些毛巾
Frank, more towels!
毛巾 他妈的就没有人给我一条毛巾吗
Towels! Will somebody
give me a fucking towel?
Frank 他们想知道她有没有吃药
Frank, they want to know
if she took any pills.
爸 爸
Dad! Dad?!
-你没事的
-我也不知道
STEVE: You're good.
I'm not sure.
你可以看到我吗
Can you see me?
帮我抬着她的脚
Frank Frank
Help me with her feet,
Frank. Frank?
过来这
Get... Get over here!
听得到我吗
听得到我吗 呼吸
You with me?
You with me? Breathe.
你会好起来的 好吗
慢慢来 你会好起来的
You're gonna be good, okay?
Slow, slow. You're gonna
就 只是 没事了
你现在很好 你现在很好
be good. It's just... It's fine.
You're fine. You're fine.
为什么Frank没有来
Why didn't Frank come?
我不知道 Debs
I don't know, Debs.
我了个去
哥们 如果你再说一次
Holy fuck.
Dude, if you say that
等我们回家的时候我要把你丢到
one more time, I'm gonna throw
you in the oven with that
烤火鸡的烤箱里面 知道吗
好的好的 我错了
turkey when we get home, okay?
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
你联系Lip了吗
You try Lip again?
是的 留言了
Yeah, just left a message.
WOMAN:
Miss Gallagher?
Debs 呆我这
Debs, stay with me.
她怎么样
How is she?
她稳定下来了
噢 感谢上帝
She's stable.
Oh, thank God.
我们要留院72小时
确保她不会再
We're gonna hold her for 72
hours, make sure she doesn't try
伤害她自己
to harm herself again.
她有精神病
She's bipolar?
好的 我们会在她吃药平静之后
Okay, we'll get her back
让她回去
我们可以见她吗
on her meds and leveled out.
Can we see her?
不 现在不可以
她吃了很多镇定剂
No, not right now.
She's heavily sedated.
你该回家了
不好意思
You should go
home. Excuse me.
你还好吗
You okay?
-Lip刚打电话给我
-他要来吗
Lip just called.
He's coming?
Karen正在楼上生孩子
Karen's having her baby upstairs.
我了个去
Holy fuck!
产房往这走吗
我要做姑姑了
Is Maternity this way?
I'm gonna be an aunt!
我要有一个可以痛打一顿打的侄子了
I'm gonna have a nephew I can beat up.
(grunts)
为什么我不能剖腹产
Why can't I just get a C-section?
你用不着剖腹产 亲爱的
You're too far along, sweetie.
-有的时候上帝有自己的安排 亲爱的
-去他妈的上帝
- Sometimes Mother Nature has
other plans, honey. - Fuck Mother Nature!
-她没有必要去担心她的阴道变松
-哦
- She doesn't have to worry about her vagina
getting stretched. - Ow!
你就是从
You were already
那个变松的地方出来的 Karen
pretty stretched out
down there, Karen.
我想吃药
给我药
I want drugs!
Give me drugs!
亲爱的 用力
你快好了 用力
Sweetie, push!
You're almost there. Push!
我在用力 贱人
哦 我可以看到他的头了
I am pushing, bitch.
Oh, I can see his head.
噢 我的天啊 生命的奇迹 亲爱的
Oh, my God, the miracle
of birth, sweetie!
真的太美了
It's so beautiful.
又有一个新的来访者了
More visitors.
嘿 甜心
ALANA:
Hey, sweetheart!
Oh, the Gallaghers!
派对
It's a party!
(all cheering)
我要做外婆了
I'm gonna be a grandma!
太棒了 我生孩子
Great. Let's just have the whole
Fighting Illini
干脆让整个医院的人都进来看好了
marching band in while we're at it!
Lip!
看 我的宝贝孩子出来了
Look, my baby boy's come out.
恶心
Ew.
阴道
Vagina.
对不去 兄弟 我们没有时间去买烟
Sorry we didn't have time
to buy you any cigars, man.
没事的 兄弟
Oh, no worries, man.
真好 你们这些家伙在我坐在这的时候
That's right, all you guys just
fucking whoop it up
居然在他妈的狂欢
操
while I'm sitting in here!
Fucking fuck!
好的 来了 来了 来了
DOCTOR: Okay, it's coming.
It's coming. It's coming!
呼吸 Karen
JODY:
Breathe, Karen.
你要呼吸 傻蛋
You keep breathing, fuck nut!
操 我不记得我想这么做过了
Shit, I don't know if I ever
wanna do this now.
再用一次力 Karen
One more big push, Karen.
(grunts)
(all cheering)
(baby crying)
呃 医生吗
Um, Doctor?
怎么了
What's going on?
他还好吗
Is he okay?
哦 不
Oh, no.
看起来好奇怪
That thing looks weird.
我觉得他看起来美极了
I think he looks beautiful.
他怎么了
What's wrong with him?
(baby cries)
他有唐氏综合症 Debs
He has Down Syndrome, Debs.
是的 他是亚洲人
Yeah, and he's Asian.
也许我们刚才把他倒着看了
Maybe we're just looking at him
upside down.
给你 宝贝
你现在可以抱他了
NURSE: Here you go, honey,
you can hold him now.
不 不 我不想碰他
No, no, I don't want to touch him.
你要抱着他然后说再见
You should hold him
and say good-bye.
把他拿走
Just take him away.
搞毛啊 Karen
What the fuck, Karen,
我以为你说他是我的
I thought you said it was mine?!
我跟Timmy Wong干的次数跟你一样多
I screwed Timmy Wong
as much as I screwed you.
我从来都没有说过他是你的宝宝
I never said it was your baby.
是你自己一厢情愿
You just wanted it to be.
(crying)
让Jeff和Alana来把他们该死的宝宝拿走
Go tell Jeff and Alana to come
get their fucking baby.
(crying continues)
? The fire, the wine,
the bed and you... ?
? This crimson light,
I find the truth ?
? And truth is like a punch or two ?
Lip?
? It hits you hard
and knocks you through ?
让他走
Let him go.
? So I get on the road
and ride to you ?
? I get on the road and ride to you ?
? One tender payment for our sins ?
? You are the drug that I can't quit ?
? So I get on the road
and ride to you ?
? I get on the roadand right ?
? The wheel, it settles in my hands ?
? This is the measure of this man ?
? I point the car at north, at you ?
(alarm beeping)
? My route has scarred
the country through ?
来 Sheila 快点
JODY:
Come on, Sheila! Hurry up!
孩子在我的
I got the baby!
孩子在我的 孩子在我的
快点 快点
I got the baby! I got the baby!
Come on! Come on!
我 我的天
哦 上帝啊
Oh, my God!
Oh, Lord!
【贴吧无耻之徒字幕组】
【翻译】NG 胡小贼 Dream 哎呦 五先生 郭巍
【校对】NG 胡小贼 Dream 五先生 郭巍
【后期】Mark
? My route has scarred
the country through ?
【贴吧无耻之徒字幕组】
【翻译】NG 胡小贼 Dream 哎呦 五先生 郭巍
【校对】NG 胡小贼 Dream 五先生 郭巍
【后期】Mark
(both whooping)
【百度贴吧无耻之徒字幕组】